Test Automation Engineer

Rafał Michalski +48 508 273 006

<u>rafallovesworking@gmail.com</u> https://rafalloves.dev/

Key skills and qualifications:

I am a proactive and development oriented test automation engineer who is capable of dealing with every QA task. I can easily identify, describe and automate test pipelines and present results in a Business-friendly manner.

Commercial experience in software testing, analytical skills - test case identification, writing steps and acceptance criterias, test implementation in Cypress or Selenium, setting up CI pipelines, test results interpretation and presentation. Ability to test applications written in any framework.

Key competences:

- Selenium, Appium, Rest Assured
- Cypress
- Spring Boot
- Postman, Git, Jira
- Java, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3

Professional experience:

02.2022 - now **Ework Group**

Tester Automatyzujący

Independent Maintainer and Developer of two Selenium frameworks with a parallel test execution.

Responsibilities:

- Engineering of test framework suitable for company business needs.
- Writing and maintaining tests
- Responsibility for testing of two services of critical business
- API and GUI tests, that use newest features of Selenium 4
- Creating module for automation of test result propagation between TestNG based tests and TestRail.

10.2021 - 12.2021 **C&F S. A.**

Test Automation Engineer

Test automation for pharmaceutical plant management system for a top pharmaceutical company.

Responsibilities:

- Working on test automation cases based on given criteria. Technologies used: Java, Selenium. UI and API testing.
- Code refactoring and maintenance.

08.2021 – now **Apricot Sp. z o.o.**

Test Automation Engineer

E-commerce website testing

 Independent project. Identification and description of test cases. Test automation (Cypress, Javascript), code documentation in a Business-friendly manner. Bug finding and reporting.

Responsibilities:

- Cooperation with a client in order to find out Business needs.
- Establishing test cases and priority of their delivery.
- Coding.
- Business friendly presentation and teaching non IT client how to use my software.

2021 - now Freelancer

Test Automation Engineer

Selected projects:

- Testing an app of a startup that connects lawyers with people in need of legal advice.
- Testing a fintech app for large enterprises 3 dimensional Excel - like spreadsheet, with sorting and filtering capabilities.
- Testing unfinished app with no GUI, using only API.

Education:

2010 – 2012 University of Warsaw

Mathematics

2009 – 2012 Warsaw School of Economics Quantitative Methods and Information Systems

Languages:

English: Fluent (C1)

German: Intermediate - reading (B1)

French: Beginner - reading (A1)

Polish: Native.